flyheightvideos.com 2019-05-14

# Privacy Policy - FlyHeight

**Privacy policy**

 **Analyze Data**

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server does not recognize any information regarding the domain or e-mail address. IP addresses are not logged 

 **Collecting e-mail Addresses**

We collect the e-mail addresses of Flyheight Delivery recipients and senders for the purpose of logging and measuring usage. Flyheight does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with nonaffiliated companies. 

 **Certain Exceptional Disclosures**

We may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct or potential threats to the physical safety of any person. Disclosure may be required by law or if we receive legal process. 

 **Use of Cookies**

Flyheight uses cookies to store the preferences of users. 

 **File Transfer Security  **

We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. Files stored for delivery are only accessible by Flyheight and through the clickable link generated for your recipient. All files stored for delivery are deleted when they expire. 

 **Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

 **Third Party Cookies**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**Our Policy Towards Children’s Information**

This Service is not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us immediately here: https://flyheightvideos.com/contact . If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.

 **Effective Date: December 1, 2015  **
